Pulling down all the data will reduce latency and maximize the
battery efficiency. But it's unlikely the user is going to read every
article. So you'd just be wasting a lot of bandwidth. Downloading
all the articles without pictures actually doesn't improve our efficiency if
you're just downloading the front page, because you'll still need to
activate the radio to download those pictures whenever an article is
selected. The right answer is to get the headlines and the
articles linked to from that front page, 'cause they're the most likely
to be read as the user starts
browsing through the app. You can then incrementally
download more articles each time the user moves
into an area you haven't pre-fetched for yet.